hitorikiri de hiza o kakaete
All on my own, I hugged my knees
ikiteru koto mo mienaku natteta
I couldn’t even see that I was still alive
yogorekitta kienai kizu o
My wound was filthy and wouldn’t disappear
itametsukenagara nandomo nadeta
I kept on caressing it and only hurt it more
odayaka na kin’iro no yume   kaze ga kiita kotoba
Dreams that glowed in gold, soft and peaceful, words witnessed by the wind
yururi to mazariau you na yawaraka na omoi o
Slowly mixing into all the tender feelings in my heart
ame no hi mo, hare no hi mo, itsu no hi mo aishiteta
Through the rainy days, through the sunny days, every single day I loved you
sore dake wa ima mo mada zutto kawari wa shinai
That’s the only thing I can say will always stay the same
dakedo yakusoku wa hatasenai mama
But time went on, the promise unfulfilled
yowai watashi o mamoru kokoro ga
My heart protected me, weak as I am,
sotto se o oshite hitori de mukau
and gently pushed me on, walking on my own,
ashita no hibi ga kagayake to waratta
while wishing for tomorrow’s days to shine, with a smile
itsuka, itsu no hi ka
One day, one of these days
waraeru hibi ni aruiteku
I’ll be able to smile
itsuka, itsu no hi ka...
One day, one of these days...
kanashisa o kanjiru koto wa ima dake wa yurushite
Please allow me the freedom to feel sadness just for now
owari no kowareta hibi o owari ni suru kara
The end to these days is broken, but I will bring an end to them
ame no hi mo, hare no hi mo, itsu no hi mo suki datta
Through the rainy days, through the sunny days, every single day you were in my heart
sore dake wa ima mo mada zutto kawari wa shinai
That’s the only thing I can say will always stay the same
soshite yakusoku o shinji, yabureru
And I will go down believing the promise true
yowai kokoro o tsutsumu ryoute de
With my fragile heart held in two cupped hands
afureru namida   nugutte kureru
you’ll gently wipe away my overflowing tears
yasashii anata ni tsutaeru n da
and for your kindness I’ll say to you
“arigatou”
“Thank you”